becauseisaidiwould.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy | because I said I would.

**Updated as of  9/29/2014**

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you provide it to our site including when you register at the online store in connection with an order, submit to “Share Your Story,” subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.  As applicable, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

**When You Provide Your Email Address**  
When you sign up for our newsletter, the email address you provide for may be used to send you occasional company news and updates.

When you register with the site in connection with order processing, the email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private financial information (credit cards, social security numbers, specific payments, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**When you share your promise, story or comment**  
**When you share a promise card, personal story or comment on another story, you are consenting to publication of materials which may include personally identifiable or other private information.     Additional terms for Share Your Story are found here.**

**Do** **we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties only:

  * In connection with your contributions which you opt to post publicly on the website.
  * To provide services through trusted third parties assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential (e.g. credit card processor).
  * For monitoring, marketing, demographic, and promotional purposes as well as to assist us in improving the website, subject to confidentiality obligations.
  * When we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety or we find, in our discretion, that your actions on our website warrant outside investigation.
  * When we sell or otherwise transfer such information to a successor or subsidiary of bisiw, who would be bound by the then-current bisiw Privacy Policy.
  * When you specifically consent.

**Except as specified above, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information**.  
We may share your non-personally identifiable information with third parties only:

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses, to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance and Do Not Track browser signals**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  We currently do not actively respond to Do Not Track browser signals and do not authorize the collection of personal information from users through technologies deployed in advertising on the site.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), and we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  If you are under 13 years old, do not submit any information to our website.

**Online Privacy Policy Only                                                                     **  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Opting-Out**  
You may opt-out of having your personal information collected or used by contacting us by e-mail or regular mail using the contact information below.

**Reviewing and Updating Your Personal Information**  
You may request via e-mail or regular mail that we provide you with the personal information we have concerning you.  Once you receive this information, you may request that we modify or remove any of your personal information.  We reserve the right to verify your identity before sending you this information, and to securely retain information for law enforcement purposes.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by: emailing [contact@becauseisaidiwould.com](mailto:contact@becauseisaidiwould.com), calling 216 226 3770 or by writing us at 20525 Center Ridge Rd. Suite 500, Rocky River, OH 44116.  Feel free to contact us with any questions or concerns.
